谢谢啦  Dan  正如我们之前所说的  我们在整个课程中都将使用Android Studio
Thanks, Dan. As mentioned earlier, we'll be using Android Studio throughout this
Android Studio是基于Intellij的专门为Android应用开发定制的IDE
course. It's an IntelliJ -based IDE that is optimized specifically for
由于现在Android Studio还处于测试开发阶段  所以
Android development. It's still in beta development, so
您的版本看起来可能略有不同  但是没有关系
your version may look slightly different, but that's okay.
Android Studio的核心功能是没有改变的  如果你还没有安装Android Studio
The core functionality should still be the same. If you haven't installed it
现在请您按照详细说明和下面的链接进行操作
yet, take a moment to do that now using the detailed instructions provided in
在说明中还提到了您还需要安装Android Studio的支持库
the link below. You'll also need to install the support library and that's also
需要注意的是  Android SDK是自动包含在内的
included in the instructions. Note that the SDK is included automatically, so
所以你不需要单独安装Android SDK  如果安装SDK有困难
you don't need to install that separately. If you're having difficulties, no
完全不需要担心  我们非常理解一上手就跑通并正确设置是非常棘手的
worries at all. We totally understand because it can be tricky to get everything
您可以在线搜索其他人是否也遇到过类似的问题
set up properly. You can search online for people who have a similar issue or
是否含有解决问题的链接  如果你仍然需要帮助
there's a troubleshooting link included below. If you still need help, you can
你也可以在我们论坛的讨论区提问  一旦你安装成功
ask a question in our discussion forum as well. Once you install it, open it and
打开Android Studio并且在你进行下一步之前请检查更新  当你完成时选中该复选框
you can check for updates before proceeding. Check this box when you're done.